all-guitar-chords.com 2005-12-12

# Privacy statement

**Privacy Statement and Other Policies for www.all-guitar-chords.com**

All Guitar Chords has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: All Guitar Chords (http://www.all-guitar-chords.com) 

**Computer Tracking and Cookies**

This site uses outside ad companies to display ads on this site. These ads may contain cookies. Although this site uses cookies in parts of this Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by ad companies, and this site does not access that information. 

Our web sites are not set up to track, collect or distribute personal information not entered by visitors. Our site logs do generate certain kinds of non-identifying site usage data, such as the number of hits and visits to our sites. This information is used for internal purposes by technical support staff to provide better services to the public and may also be provided to others, but again, the statistics contain no personal information and cannot be used to gather such information. 

All Guitar Chords uses non-identifying cookies to provide easier site navigation and access to forms. You can still use the All Guitar Chords sites if your browser is set to reject cookies. Our cookies do not generate personal data, do not read personal data from your machine and are never tied to anything that could be used to identify you. 

**Links on the Site**

This site contains links to other sites. All Guitar Chords is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

Other sites may contain links to All Guitar Chords, along with a banner or text link to refer them here from other sites who have exchanged preferential links with this site. All Guitar Chords is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites and they do not share any information with us or us with them. 

**Contacting the Web Site**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:   
webmaster@all-guitar-chords.com
